[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "111020pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 34, "question": "How would you describe the mood there?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "describe", "the", "mood", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 35, "answer": "It's just been electric all day, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "just", "been", "electric", "all", "day", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111020pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", ":", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "Do we have a clearer picture?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "we", "have", "a", "clearer", "picture", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "Well, this is -- this is our understanding at the moment.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "this", "is", "--", "this", "is", "our", "understanding", "at", "the", "moment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111020pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 64, "question": "What have I done to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "have", "I", "done", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "Extraordinary.", "answer_tokens": ["Extraordinary", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111020pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "RB", ",", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 72, "question": "Was he really hit by crossfire as they tried to take him to the hospital as the NTC claims, or was this a mob out of control and someone decided to execute him on the spot?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "he", "really", "hit", "by", "crossfire", "as", "they", "tried", "to", "take", "him", "to", "the", "hospital", "as", "the", "NTC", "claims", ",", "or", "was", "this", "a", "mob", "out", "of", "control", "and", "someone", "decided", "to", "execute", "him", "on", "the", "spot", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", ",", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 73, "answer": "Dan, for now, thank you very much.", "answer_tokens": ["Dan", ",", "for", "now", ",", "thank", "you", "very", "much", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NTC"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111020pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 85, "question": "And I guess the other question I'd ask you is, do you care?", "question_tokens": ["And", "I", "guess", "the", "other", "question", "I", "'d", "ask", "you", "is", ",", "do", "you", "care", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 86, "answer": "I care about one thing.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "care", "about", "one", "thing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Libya"]}, "docId": "111020pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "How do you see the future for Libya mapping out?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "see", "the", "future", "for", "Libya", "mapping", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBG", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "Well, the future for Libya is going to very bright.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "future", "for", "Libya", "is", "going", "to", "very", "bright", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Libya"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111020pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 121, "question": "And Your Highness, do you hope to have a role yourself in any future Libyan government?", "question_tokens": ["And", "Your", "Highness", ",", "do", "you", "hope", "to", "have", "a", "role", "yourself", "in", "any", "future", "Libyan", "government", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP$", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 122, "answer": "No, I'm not talking about government.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "talking", "about", "government", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["2 million barrels"]}, "docId": "111020pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ":", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", ",", "NN", "RB", "TO", "CD", "TO", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "What happens about oil now?", "question_tokens": ["What", "happens", "about", "oil", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "Well, oil going to be -- going to be developed, bring back to 1.6 to 2 million barrels a day.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "oil", "going", "to", "be", "--", "going", "to", "be", "developed", ",", "bring", "back", "to", "1.6", "to", "2", "million", "barrels", "a", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111020pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 148, "question": "When you saw the video footage, how did you feel?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "saw", "the", "video", "footage", ",", "how", "did", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 149, "answer": "It is an understatement if I tell you that -- I can't even describe.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "an", "understatement", "if", "I", "tell", "you", "that", "--", "I", "ca", "n't", "even", "describe", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111020pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "Where were you when you heard the news?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "were", "you", "when", "you", "heard", "the", "news", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "I was in my office when we first heard the news.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "in", "my", "office", "when", "we", "first", "heard", "the", "news", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Libya"]}, "docId": "111020pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 179, "question": "What is your view of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "view", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 180, "answer": "Well, I certainly think we should be talking to the transitional national council as it moves to establish a government in Libya.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "certainly", "think", "we", "should", "be", "talking", "to", "the", "transitional", "national", "council", "as", "it", "moves", "to", "establish", "a", "government", "in", "Libya", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111020pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "Where does this rank in terms of significance, the demise of Moammar Gadhafi, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "does", "this", "rank", "in", "terms", "of", "significance", ",", "the", "demise", "of", "Moammar", "Gadhafi", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "This is a huge milestone.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "a", "huge", "milestone", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Moammar Gadhafi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111020pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "You know the scenario there, isn't there, about how he met his maker?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "the", "scenario", "there", ",", "is", "n't", "there", ",", "about", "how", "he", "met", "his", "maker", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "There is.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Syria"]}, "docId": "111020pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 215, "question": "Do you think that we're seeing a whole sea change here in terms of American foreign policy?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "that", "we", "'re", "seeing", "a", "whole", "sea", "change", "here", "in", "terms", "of", "American", "foreign", "policy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 216, "answer": "Well, I think this is historic, and I don't think it's going to be a precedent that is going to lead us to move into Syria or other places.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "this", "is", "historic", ",", "and", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "a", "precedent", "that", "is", "going", "to", "lead", "us", "to", "move", "into", "Syria", "or", "other", "places", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111020pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "What do you think will happen in Libya in the short to middle term?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "will", "happen", "in", "Libya", "in", "the", "short", "to", "middle", "term", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "Well, I have a lot of friends who are pretty wary.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "have", "a", "lot", "of", "friends", "who", "are", "pretty", "wary", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Libya"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111020pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", ",", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "WP", "VBD", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "What were your thoughts today when you heard that he's finally gone?", "question_tokens": ["What", "were", "your", "thoughts", "today", "when", "you", "heard", "that", "he", "'s", "finally", "gone", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "Well, the first thought was, this was an erratic mysterious who was murderous and defiant to the end.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "first", "thought", "was", ",", "this", "was", "an", "erratic", "mysterious", "who", "was", "murderous", "and", "defiant", "to", "the", "end", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mark Kimmitt"]}, "docId": "111020pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 271, "question": "This was a triumph for the moment, the question now is, can we build on that triumph and help the Libyans become what they can become?", "question_tokens": ["This", "was", "a", "triumph", "for", "the", "moment", ",", "the", "question", "now", "is", ",", "can", "we", "build", "on", "that", "triumph", "and", "help", "the", "Libyans", "become", "what", "they", "can", "become", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NNPS", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "Well, it's interesting you say that, I've got someone you now well, General Mark Kimmitt, with me.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "interesting", "you", "say", "that", ",", "I", "'ve", "got", "someone", "you", "now", "well", ",", "General", "Mark", "Kimmitt", ",", "with", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dan Rather"]}, "docId": "111020pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 277, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 278, "answer": "Well, I think, first of all, Dan Rather was precise in his forecast and I very much associate myself with those comments as well.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "Dan", "Rather", "was", "precise", "in", "his", "forecast", "and", "I", "very", "much", "associate", "myself", "with", "those", "comments", "as", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111020pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "Or does that in itself concern you?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "does", "that", "in", "itself", "concern", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "Well, it doesn't concern me.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "does", "n't", "concern", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111020pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "Isn't this extraordinary what is going on?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "this", "extraordinary", "what", "is", "going", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "It's absolutely extraordinary.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "absolutely", "extraordinary", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["February"], "ORGANIZATION": ["NTC"]}, "docId": "111020pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 323, "question": "Are they equipped, do you think, the NTC, to build a new government?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "they", "equipped", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "the", "NTC", ",", "to", "build", "a", "new", "government", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "DT", "NNP", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 324, "answer": "Well, the NTC has, I think, made great strides since the uprising started in February.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "NTC", "has", ",", "I", "think", ",", "made", "great", "strides", "since", "the", "uprising", "started", "in", "February", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NTC"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Libya"]}, "docId": "111020pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "TO", "RB", "VB", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 336, "question": "Is it harder when you have so many different tribal elements?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "harder", "when", "you", "have", "so", "many", "different", "tribal", "elements", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "I think the divisions that we're seeing in Libya and the fault lines that I just mentioned a minute ago do make it difficult, I think, to really go very quickly, that is at least in a kind of democratic direction, the way that we in the west would like to see.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "divisions", "that", "we", "'re", "seeing", "in", "Libya", "and", "the", "fault", "lines", "that", "I", "just", "mentioned", "a", "minute", "ago", "do", "make", "it", "difficult", ",", "I", "think", ",", "to", "really", "go", "very", "quickly", ",", "that", "is", "at", "least", "in", "a", "kind", "of", "democratic", "direction", ",", "the", "way", "that", "we", "in", "the", "west", "would", "like", "to", "see", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gadhafi"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "111020pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "Well, I think everyone in the Gadhafi regime that was involved with terrorist attacks against America should be held accountable.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "everyone", "in", "the", "Gadhafi", "regime", "that", "was", "involved", "with", "terrorist", "attacks", "against", "America", "should", "be", "held", "accountable", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jalil", "Gadhafi", "John"]}, "docId": "111020pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", ":", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "TO", "VB", ",", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "Or are you happy that he was possibly executed in fairly brutal fashion by the rebels?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "are", "you", "happy", "that", "he", "was", "possibly", "executed", "in", "fairly", "brutal", "fashion", "by", "the", "rebels", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "Well, a month ago, I had met with the current Libyan president -- President Jalil, who pledged to me that he and his regime wanted to bring Gadhafi to justice, not only for the murder of -- of John and other innocent civilians, but also for the murder of his people.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "a", "month", "ago", ",", "I", "had", "met", "with", "the", "current", "Libyan", "president", "--", "President", "Jalil", ",", "who", "pledged", "to", "me", "that", "he", "and", "his", "regime", "wanted", "to", "bring", "Gadhafi", "to", "justice", ",", "not", "only", "for", "the", "murder", "of", "--", "of", "John", "and", "other", "innocent", "civilians", ",", "but", "also", "for", "the", "murder", "of", "his", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]